[Music]
hey and welcome i'm hammeh and fresh out
of the overwatch to beta we have the
junker queen odessa des stones voice
lines and interactions here's what i can
find from the beta so far both in terms
of pre-game lines specific map
interactions interactions with
particular heroes and specific kill
quotes now if you like these videos and
would like to see more as well as
discovering overwatch law interactions
and voice lines ever since overwatch
launched way back in 2016 i've got you
covered throw a like subscribe to the
channel and comment below with what
you'd like to see
my throne is where i say it is
is this one a scrap or a heist
i wasn't listening
the knife's called gracie the axe is
carnage and me
i'm your queen
so
here's the plan do what i do listen to
what i say and don't screw this up
before we go out there i gotta warn you
i'm gonna yell at you a lot
not because i don't like you or because
i care or any of that it's just because
i'm really good at this
one
ain't easy is it
being in charge of killers and mad men
no
but i welcome the challenge
is where i've met mossies with more
brains than you forks with all due
respect milady i believe that's a knock
against the junkertown education system
we've got an education system didn't i
say i'd rip out your tongue if i saw you
again
my queen your voice ever sonorous is
like a gentle waterfall upon my ears
five the ears are next brown is where
else i'm trying to ask everybody this
what is your favorite animal is there a
kind of dingo that is also a shark
uh yeah i can see it
doctor have i really got to eat
vegetables it's like crunch crunch
crunch how long have i got to chew these
is where mako the wreckers want your
back thought you might like to know
[Music]
they'll hate that i'll pass it along
is where are you on average more
mechanical or more human
why
trying to figure out whether to scrap
you for parts
hmm
consider the railgun before you decide
rhone is where i could have run
overwatch much better than you
and what would you have done differently
i would have caught all the bad guys
then cut their heads off
tempting
is where there's nothing about you and
my files no images no documents
nothing yeah well i'm what's the word
starts with e enigmatic that's the one
and don't you forget it
my throne is where how many widows have
you made roughly
i do not keep track
well i'm pretty sure i'm ahead
got any room in that mech champ i want
to take some souvenirs
champ i need you to make me something
else i need a slot bucket that's
bulletproof and don't you dare ask why
he says fine but give me a challenge
next time
jack i need you to make me something
else
a suit of armor right
but one that shouts my name
says fine but give me a challenge next
time
jeff i need you to make me something
else a robot guard dog for me dirt
garden maybe it can fly you decide
says a challenge next time
but he
dank i need you to make me something
else
a grenade launcher with one trigger
three barrels paint glitter
and nails
he says fine but give me a challenge
next time
anyone want to hear my favorite joke
about the periodic table not unless you
want that table broken over your head
you look like a bruiser
wanna be my bodyguard
huh
i think you can take care of yourself
put a dent in your armor there
quit hiding behind your shield big girl
down you go big man
wish one of those big underwater robots
would attack
i don't need a mech to fight them
there you go what did you think of the
junker queen's lines if you like this
video throw a like subscribe comment in
the comments below with other videos
you'd like to see i am catching up on
overwatch lore comics animated short
analysis and more of all new heroes maps
and everything i've done for years so if
you'd like to see more of overwatch's
law and history do check out the
playlist here cheers for tuning in i've
been hammy take it easy
you